Is there such a thing?
All right, we're done with the seven bullets.
I don't know.
Oh, we're live right now.
I have no idea.
Oh, man, I totally forgot.
I'll just write it down as I go.
It's a little bit slower than usual, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Let's write it down properly.
Hmm...
Let's see...
It's 24.
What's it called?
24?
Do you have some paper to write the formula on? Never mind, let's just use it like this.
What?
Six, seven, eight, nine, nine, three, two, one.
Uh, wait a minute.
You're probably wondering what I'm looking at.
No, of course you're not.
I'm testing you right now.
And it's math.
We're doing an arithmetic test.
Well...
I don't know.
Oh, okay.
What's the least common multiple?
I really don't know.I really don't get it.
So what's the greatest common divisor?
It's a divisor.
What's a divisor?
Oh!
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry!
I think I got it.
Oh, my God.
18 and 24?
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'll just erase it.
What?
What does that mean?
I thought you said it was a common divisor.
Isn't the first common multiple 1?
If you multiply it by one, yes, it is.
No, it's not.
What's a divisor?
I can't even do normal division!
If I sell a 4,800 yen item for 1,920 yen, what is the discount?
This discount system is very hard, isn't it?
I can't do it.
I... I... I...
Oh, no!
What?
Which side would you rather take, 4 apples for 360 yen
Which side would you choose between 4 apples for 360 yen and 7 apples for 560 yen?
Answer Difference
Let's see...Let's see...
Do I have to write an equation for this?
If I just get the answer right...
Is it OK?
S
But there are three more questions. I'm sorry, folks, but I'm not sure I'm up to the task of dealing with all those people's stupidity.
I'm not getting it at all.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Which is the best deal?
You sell apples of good quality, right?
Brand name apples.
It could be a lot, or it could be the opposite.
So this should work.
If you sell a 4,800 yen item for 1,920 yen, what is the discount?
That's quite a discount.
I see.
Yes, like this.
I have no idea what a four-foot something is.
What's the discount?
What's the least common multiple?
I remember that... we used to do that all the time... greatest common divisor...
I know what divisors are.
By the way, don't you know, Subi?
I did it last night and got an 80!
Wow!
That's 18 and 24, so that means it's related to both.
You don't tell me anything. It's too hard.
That's harsh.
No, it's something like a 30, maybe.
Multiples.Multiples
I'm shocked that you can do normal division.
Like three-digit and three-digit divisors.
It's bad.
That's a bad division thing.
You're not supposed to use an iPhone or something for this.
It's no good. It's too hard to calculate. That's fine, it's the 21st century.
Okay, so excuse me, live audience. What a surprise!
This week's shift is in the void. I am surprisingly, kind of smart.
I don't know whether you can study or not.
I don't know whether you can study or not. Isn't that the same price? He was doing a lot of calculations even before that. That's right.
But you can do it even without the paper. No, I already wrote it down in here.
Ha-ha-ha. I know, I know. I know a lot of things.
Yes, I know. If you can't do it anymore, please give up.
Oh, I made a mistake writing this.
Yes.
It took me about a minute to finish it.
I made a mistake in the formula.
I made a mistake.
I was getting by with arithmetic back then.
I did about 50 years ago.
But we probably didn't do that four-legged thing when we were kids.
I've never seen that before.
I wrote the same answer on the wrong page.
I don't know...
I really can't do it.
The last one's not appropriate.
All have been submitted.
What a disappointment!Oh no, that's frustrating.
I'm doing my best to get the answers.
Hey, no.
No, I didn't get them all.
They're laughing at me
And there's a lot of that going around too.
There's a lot of that.
There's also a lot of this kind of movement.
Erm...
Is this a close call?
I don't know.
Well, sure, but... but I really don't think I can do it... even if I could... even if I could... even if I could... even if I couldn't...
I don't even use it anymore... all my arithmetic... it's all done by Quan, the app that gives you the formulas!
Modern kids! Wow, it's really elementary school, right? These are elementary school problems, right?
I didn't even see fractions in the elementary school problems.
I really thought there'd be a lot of formulas.
I'm good at that too.
I'm really pissed off that you're giving all the others a "X".
I'm not good at it.
That's not the same thing as the least common multiple.
That's a cylinder.
A cylinder.
I made a mistake.
What is it? Water.
Water.
What?
That's it.
Oh, yeah!
What?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.Wow, what a score!
45 points!
Wow!
Really?
Oh, man.
Two losses in a row.
Isn't that a triangular pyramid?
The bottom of the cylinder is...
Yikes.
Wow, that's that way.
It's got columns on it.
Sixty percent off?
I got a hunch.
It's not 50% off. Why is it 60% off?
Forty percent is 1,920 yen. Forty percent of 4,800 yen is 1,920 yen.
Oh, so that's what it is!
Oh no!
If we've gone this far, we're all the same, aren't we?
Finally!
No, I really don't want to do it. They'll know I can't do it at all.
You know what? I'm a little nervous too.
What's the score?
Fifty-five!
That's amazing!
That's the best I could do.
That's what I'm talking about.
What, what, what, what? Wait a minute, you mean the answer to the addition question?
Wow! It's a sum!
It's harmony! Seki!It's harmony! It's Seki!
What number is the answer to subtraction?
The difference.
That's right. Oh, that's right. What's the divisor?
Small. What's small? What kind of letter is it? Yokohama Ginmei?
Oh, yes!
"Small" is small division.
Oh, okay, let's get "small", Johnny.
Like "run," "tak," "yokohama," "ginmei," "yokohama,
It's the greatest common divisor.
What's the greatest common divisor? Those two numbers are 18 divided by 6 and 3, and then 24 divided by 6 and, what's it called?
And 24 is divided by 6 and 3, and then by 6 and 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and then by 4, and so on.
Oh, you mean 6, 4 x 6 24 and 3 x 6 18? I see...
What's the greatest common divisor? It's a multiple.
Oh, I get it! What does that mean? When you multiply 18 and 24 by one and then 18 plus 18 equals 2424.
When you get two numbers that are the same number. That number?
Oh, my God! I got it wrong!
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
I don't know what it means at all.
I didn't understand at all!
Well, well, well, well... Good evening, everyone.
Even though I'm tired from the test... I'm going to Starbucks after this...
Maybe we'll go to Starbucks afterwards...
Let's go home and play soccer... let's play baseball... let's play baseball...
So, let's go back to the park.
You guys will charge me, so...
I'm so quick to take advantage of punishments like this...
You're right! It's just like a flower!
That's it!
They're probably all oohing and aahing in front of the TV.Maybe we're all oohing and aahing in front of the TV.
Or in Dragon Ball terms, it's like this.
Thank you very much.
So I'd like to start the recording again.
Well, I'm sorry to say that next week will fly by so fast.
It's already the weekend. I mean, it's already October.
I'm so happy!
I can't keep up with the time!
So, first of all, I've received a lot of letters from you all, so let me read them now.
First of all...
Let's see...
I've been getting a lot of letters this week, and it's still hot during the day, but I've been going out a little bit.
It's still hot in the daytime, but it's starting to feel like going out.
It's still hot in the daytime, but I'm finally ready to go out.
Insects are okay, right?
Some insects are okay, right?
Maybe some things are okay.
Some things are fine.
Some things are.
Here's a good story.
I saw a cockroach in the wild the other day.
You see a lot of them, don't you?
Yeah, I guess so.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is Mr. Yuki of Zadar in Kashiwa City, Chiba Prefecture.
Last week, when I was commuting to work, I saw something buzzing on the platform of the station nearest my house.
When I approached it, I found a rather large male kokuwa.
I didn't want to leave it alone to be trampled or become food for crows or something.
But I couldn't go back to my house in time.
If I buy him well, I will be able to see him again next year after he has passed the winter.I protected it and took it straight to work, and then I brought it home to set up its living environment. If I buy it well, I can see it survive the winter and be healthy again next year, so I want to make sure I do it right.
Unlike cicadas, they're not like cicadas.
I had some insect jelly at home.
Not many of them. - No. - You're okay with insects?
It has no horns.
And the legs are just like cockroaches.
Don't sound like a bitter commentator. The show is getting warm and fuzzy.
It's got horns and a chin, but no feet.
It looks like a cockroach!
But it's big... for a cockroach.
It's cute... really cute... and... well... there's a lot of food in the world... but... this week... you're all eating that bread.
This week, we've had a lot of breads, especially breads.
Usually 70% are noodles, but this week there's a lot of bread.
I'm just saying, this is amazing.
Thank you, Mr. Chulman, for Tokyo and Itabashi. I had a sandwich with a lot of corned beef.
Absolutely delicious! This is amazing!
I don't know if I've ever had corned beef before.
I don't really remember.
It's true, they don't come out that often these days.
Yes, I know. Stick it in and spin it around.
Nozaki's corned beef.
We did this a lot.
Why do they have to do that?
Why not Copper?
There must be a reason.
I haven't seen it lately.
There was something to keep the line up, but I forgot about it
Let's see, wait a minute
Um, so...
corned beefcorned beef
Ready?
There we go.
Wow, that's a good one.
Wow. Lots of veggies.
I like it.
This looks good.
Potatoes.
And what's this?
There's a character that probably looks like...
Rod character.
Looks delicious!
I love it!
I love corned beef.
Sometimes you just want to eat it for nothing, right? Yes, I do, but there aren't many supermarkets that sell it.
In the old days, every household had a can of Nozaki's corned beef, and everyone used to open it.
And also...
Oh, this is amazing too!
What's this?
A sandwich made with bread I thought up myself.
Thank you very much. Good evening, everyone.
I'm sending you a picture of a sandwich I've been into recently, which can be easily eaten without a knife.
It may be a little hard for over-masters to eat.
What's with the big mouth?
I'm not the only one after that, am I?
So...
There it is! Cucumbers! Whole cucumbers, or rather, whole cucumbers, with mayonnaise.
Wow! A ham subti! That's good, ham!
That's good, isn't it? It's delicious!
Really? I've seen cucumbers sliced thin, but they don't have the same presence.Really? Cucumbers are sliced thin, so you see them a lot, but they don't have the same presence.
No, no, no, no...
I mean, cucumbers pickled in a cucumber. Last time I was back in Aichi, I had cucumbers with just white broth.
Why the aggressive face?
I ate it like this... it's summer... summer... I know some of you don't like cucumbers...
You know, we don't like cucumbers.
Nigati, you know, has an aroma that comes out when it is crisped. They react to it.
Someone is eating cucumbers, right? I said, "Someone is eating a cucumber. Do you have any?
You can eat it anytime.
Next time, we'll eat it together right in front of you. I'll eat it right in front of you.
Can I ask you to follow me a little?
Why did you hit me so hard?
I'm not kidding.
Everything tastes better when it's dipped in white sauce. Cucumbers, tomatoes, okra, etc.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, I understand if you like that cucumber.
It's delicious. Have you finished growing them?
Do you feel like all you've shown us is our shabby place?
Oh!
From Mr. Diamond. Just a moment here. I know this is very personal, but thank you very much.
Um...
I will be performing in a musical called "The Girl Who Leapt Through Time" from October 6 to October 10.
This way, right? This is the one with a bang. It's called "The Time Bureau".
I'm a police officer who chases after the main characters. It's based on the story of a police officer who chases after the main characters.
We will be playing at the Nihonbashi Theater, so please come and see us. Please come and see us. It will be my first musical.
By the way, did you write the flip card yourself? I wrote it, but halfway through, I lost track of how to hold the pen, and my handwriting started to look really strange.
The overall balance of the handwriting is a bit peculiar, isn't it?
Yes, that's right. I wanted lines.
But with a sense of style.
Thank you very much.
I'm not good at keeping things level without lines. As you can see in the picture, I wobble myself.I'm not good at keeping things level without lines. As you can see from my drawings, I get wobbly myself.
Anyway, I will be doing the exhibition on October 6 and 10, so if you enjoy it, please come and visit me. Thank you very much.
So, I think it's time for me to end the live distribution now. Let's end with a few words from Kokun.
Since we are here. Please don't ask me to do this.
Please don't touch me.
You're not behaving well! What do you mean by "behavior"?
See you next week!